<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on monerostartup.com - Monero Startup Services</title>
    <link>https://www.monerostartup.com/service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on monerostartup.com - Monero Startup Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.monerostartup.com/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Plan Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.monerostartup.com/service/service4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monerostartup.com/service/service4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Monero Business Plan Competition, to be organized by us, provides a real-world experience for (aspiring) crypto entrepreneurs, promoting innovative ideas, necessary infrastructure creation and new venture creation to the entrepreneurial crypto-currency community. Participating in the competition gives community members practice in the dynamics of venture creation by developing an idea, putting together a founding team, writing a business plan, and presenting to the community and possible investors.
&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coachings</title>
      <link>https://www.monerostartup.com/service/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monerostartup.com/service/service3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Business plans, pitchdecks, financing models: These are only a few topics startups have to think about. We support you individually with our know-how, act as your sparringpartner and – if required – we can consult experienced coaches and mentors from our business-club. The business-club includes experienced investors and employers, who stand by our startups and provide feedback at each developmental stage to successfully realize the business venture. Thus, startups have an opportunity to react rapidly, trap errors and use resources effectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matchings</title>
      <link>https://www.monerostartup.com/service/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monerostartup.com/service/service1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our matchings will help to introduce you to the right contact person –  be it the CEO of a startup company, an investor, or the manager of an established company. Our highlight is the yearly Investforum Pitch-Day. This event is an extraordinary platform for capital acquisition and has established as one of the most successful matching events for venture capital in Central Germany since 2009. Here, we offer startups the possibility to present their business concepts to an international audience of investors, managers and experts. The Pitch-Day is a great opportunity for investors to get to know exciting technology companies and to prepare the ground for new financing rounds. During the Investforum Innovation-Day we get startups and established companies in touch with each other. We aim to support innovations and to generate cooperations. Pitch-Day, Innovation-Day, individual matchings: our network offers profitable and reliable contacts to all our target groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>https://www.monerostartup.com/service/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monerostartup.com/service/service2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In our workshops we share knowledge about topics like business appraisal, participation forms and agreements, development of business concepts, and taxes. Especially our Lean-Development-Workshop is interesting for startups in a very early stage. Participants learn the Lean-Startup-Method and see how they can profit from it. The project team, complemented with experts, guides through the elaboration of a strategy, how the founding idea can be transferred rapidly into practice and be peer-reviewed afterwards. You can profit from our experienced experts who convey applied knowledge in a nutshell. With us by your side, you’ll be well prepared for the day-to-day business of an entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>